[{"answer": "We don't make the laws. Nineteen is carrying, twenty is dealing. Let him be stupid", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Take over for a while. I'm getting contact high", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It was supposed to be light tonight", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Don't have one", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's all over the news", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "We are careful", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " You too. my friend, what's wrong? Why are you here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Details just open the door", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We were not", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "The door to what?  It's not like we're strangers. We were married", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "There was a ceremony", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We were not", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He wasn't even a minister. He was an astrologer", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "There was a ceremony", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He was also a minister.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He wasn't even a minister. He was an astrologer", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He was a Pisces", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He was also a minister.", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You're a Pisces", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "In the eyes of my friend we're still", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We were happy", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "In rehab they call this", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I was drowning", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We were happy", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It wasn't me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "-- inactions", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You always meant well", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Eyes are deceiving.  Congratulations", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "If I could do that, I could do anything", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "We could do anything. We could start over", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Just a contact", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "The plan", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Leave a message. my friend or I will come by later", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Nineteen is the top. I'll make two trips", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " my friend's", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Just a moment", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " my friend, it's not that at all. Is that what you think? You hate cosmetics. You don't care about it. You told me that", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Who knows what will happen", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Tour, just in time. We were out. Nineteen, right", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Some, not the whole thing.  You got hundreds", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Someone I knew died tonight", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Am I in danger", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "This was not an accident. This person was murdered", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " There is danger around you. It's very close. I'm sleepy", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I didn't know", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " She loved you. You were what she wanted to be", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Well, I got this thing to do. It's", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I'll try", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "The label for the cosmetics line", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " that place", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Me too", "docId": "Light-Sleeper.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 54}]